A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1 FA439
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1
1959-1962
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
State of New York
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA439
171 microform reels
Conditions Governing Access note
Microfilm user copies are available for research. The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original paper records is restricted.
Arrangement note
Series 37 is arranged into 4 subseries:
Subseries 1: First Administration, 1959-1962. Subseries 2: Second Administration, 1963-1966. Subseries 3: Third Administration, 1967-1970. Subseries 4: Fourth Administration, 1971-1973.
Material is arranged alphabetically by subject within each subseries.
Scope and Contents note
Major subjects contained in the files include:
Administration. Aging. Agriculture. Authorities and Commissions. Banking. Civil Defense. Commemorative Observance. Conservation. Consumers. Correction. Disasters. Discrimination. Education. Executive Clemency. Extradition. Fiscal. Fund raising. Government. Health & Sanitation. Honorary Designation. Horse Racing. Housing. Insurance. Investigations. Invitations. Judiciary. Labor. Law. Legislation. Licensing. Mental Hygiene. Military and Naval. Organizations. Parks and Recreation facilities. Personnel Administration. Politics. Property. Public Safety. Public Utilities. Public Works. Regrets. Resignations and Vacancies. Statements. Transportation. Veterans. Welfare. Youth.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aid for Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Series 37 include:
FA439A Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2
FA439B Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Series 37.3
FA439C Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Series 37.4
- First Administration, 1959-1962; 1; 171 microform reels
  - Indexing Cards (Reel 1)
  - Administration (Reel 2, Reel 3, Reel 4, Reel 5, Reel 6)
    - Executive Chamber (Reel 2, Reel 3, Reel 4)
      - Cabinet (Reel 2)
      - Duty-Officer Roster (Reel 2)
      - Equipment (Reel 2)
        - Governor's Car (Reel 2)
        - Telephone (Reel 2)
        - Equipment: General (Reel 2)
      - Governor's Itinerary (Reel 2)
        - Texas Trip (Reel 2)
        - General (Reel 2)
      - Inaugural (Reel 2)
      - Inter-Office Memos
        - Amper, Richard (Reel 2)
        - Baike, Edith (Reel 2)
        - Corbin, Sol Neil (Reel 2)
        - Dekay, Kenneth (Reel 2)
        - Doherty, Frank (Reel 2)
        - Fowler, Peggy (Reel 2)
        - Kent, Earl (Reel 2)
        - MacCrate, Robert (Reel 2)
        - Martin, June (Reel 2)
        - McManus, Robert (Reel 2)
        - Morrow, Hugh (Reel 2)
        - Musicus, Milton (Reel 2)
        - O'Donnel, Harry (Reel 2)
        - Palmer, Charles H. (Reel 2)
        - Perkine, Roswell (Reel 2)
        - Rand, Williams (Reel 2)
        - Remington, Thomas (Reel 3)
        - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Reel 3)
        - Ronan, William (Reel 3)
        - J. Root, Oren (Reel 3)
        - Savell,Isabelle (Reel 3)
        - Schuyler, C.V.R. (Reel 3)
        - Sharkey, William (Reel 3)
        - Slater, Ilene (Reel 3)
        - Spad, Carl (Reel 3)
        - Sullivan, James (Reel 3)
        - Terry, John H. (Reel 3)
        - Wainwright, C. L., Jr. (Reel 3)
        - Walsh, David H. (Reel 3)
        - Walsh, John M. (Reel 3)
        - Wheatley, Henry (Reel 3)
        - Wickman, Raymond (Reel 3)
        - Wiebe, Richard (Reel 3)
        - A. Others (Reel 3)
      - Legislative Mail Reports (Reel 3)
      - Mailing List (Reel 4)
      - Office Space (Reel 4)
      - Personnel (Reel 4)
        - Letters of Appointment & Commendation (Reel 4)
        - Staff Memo (Reel 4)
        - General (Reel 4)
      - Press Conference (Reel 4)
      - Purchases (Reel 4)
        - Credit Cards (Reel 4)
        - General (Reel 4)
      - Records (Reel 4)
      - Repairs & Alterations (Reel 4)
      - General (Reel 4)
      - Executive Mansion (Reel 4)
        - Fire (Reel 4)
        - General (Reel 4)
    - State (Reel 4, Reel 5, Reel 6)
      - Census (Reel 4)
      - Economy Reports & Savings (Reel 4)
      - Electronic Data Processing (Reel 5)
        - Lawrence, Richard (Reel 5)
        - General (Reel 5)
      - Executive Orders (Reel 5)
      - Point of Contact with Governor's Office (Reel 5)
      - Reorganization Plan March (Reel 5)
      - Status Chart (Reel 5)
      - General (Reel 5)
      - Department of
        - Cemetery Board & Division of (Reel 5)
        - Codes, Rules & Regulations (Reel 5)
        - Special Elections (Reel 5)
        - State Athletic Commission (Reel 6)
        - Upholstery & Bedding Division (Reel 6)
        - General (Reel 6)
  - Aging (Reel 6, Reel 7)
    - Problems of
      - Employment (Reel 6)
      - Housing (Reel 6)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on the Aging (Reel 6)
      - Life Article (Reel 6)
      - Pensions and Social Security (Reel 6)
      - Recreation (Reel 6)
      - Tax Exemption (Reel 7)
      - White House Conference, 1961 January (Reel 7)
      - General (Reel 7)
  - Agriculture & Markets (Reel 7, Reel 8)
    - Department of (Reel 7, Reel 8)
      - Animal Industry (Reel 7)
      - General (Reel 7)
      - Vivisection and Humane Slaughter (Reel 7)
      - State Fairs (Reel 7)
      - Meat Inspection (Rabbi Cohen) (Reel 7)
      - Food Control (Reel 7)
        - Meat Inspection (Reel 7)
        - General (Reel 8)
      - Genessee Valley Regional Market Authority (Reel 8)
      - Interdepartmental Comm. on Farm & Food Processing Labor (Reel 8)
      - General (Reel 8)
    - Products (Reel 8)
      - Apples (Reel 8)
      - Eggs (Reel 8)
      - Flower (Reel 8)
    - Food Products (Reel 8)
      - Milk (Reel 8)
        - Milk Dating (Reel 8)
        - Governor's Committee of Increased Use (Reel 8)
        - Licensing (Reel 8)
        - Marketing (Reel 8)
        - Milk Prices (Reel 8)
        - General (Reel 8)
      - Potatoes (Reel 8)
      - Sugar (Reel 8)
      - Others (Reel 8)
    - General (Reel 8)
      - Century Farm Citations (Reel 8)
      - Farm Problems & Politics (Reel 8)
      - General (Reel 8)
  - Authorities and Commissions (Reel 8, Reel 9, Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12, Reel 13)
    - Adirondack Mountain Authority (Reel 8)
    - Albany Port District Commission (Reel 8)
    - Atlantic Shorefront Commission on Protection & Preservation (Reel 8)
    - Atomic Research & Development Authority (Reel 8)
    - Bethpage Park Authority (Reel 8)
    - New York State Bridge Authority (Reel 8)
    - Buffalo Municipal Housing Authority (Reel 8)
    - Buffalo Sewer Authority (Reel 8)
    - Temporary Commission on the Capital City (Albany) (Reel 8)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission (Reel 8)
    - Constitution Revision Commission (Reel 8)
    - Constitution Revision Commission (Reel 9)
    - Delaware River Basin (Reel 9)
    - Dormitory Authority (Reel 9)
    - East Hudson River Parkway (Reel 9)
    - Temporary State Commission on Economic Expansion (Reel 9)
      - Final Report (Reel 9)
      - General (Reel 9)
    - Erie County Water Authority (Reel 9)
    - Temporary State Comm. on Governmental Operations of N.Y.C. (Reel 9)
    - Highway Finance Planning Commission (Reel 9)
    - Historic Observances Commission (Reel 9)
    - Interdepartmental Health Resources Board (Reel 9)
    - Temporary Commission on Irrigation (Reel 9)
    - Job Development (Reel 10)
    - Joint Historical Survey & Planning Commission (Reel 10)
    - Jones Beach State Park Parkway Authority (Reel 10)
    - Lake Champlain Bridge Commission (Reel 10)
    - Law Revision Commission (Reel 10)
    - Liquor Authority (Reel 10)
    - Lottery Control Commission (Reel 10)
    - Monroe County Water Authority (Reel 10)
    - Nassau County Bridge Authority (Reel 10)
    - New York Business Development Corporation (Reel 10)
    - New York-Vermont Interstate Comm. on Lake Champlain Basin (Reel 10)
    - New York City Housing Authority (Reel 10)
    - New York City Transit Authority (Reel 10)
    - Niagara Falls Bridge Commission (Reel 10)
    - Niagara Falls Frontier Port Authority (Reel 10)
    - Niagara Falls Frontier Port Authority (Reel 11)
    - Ogdensburg Bridge & Port Authority (Reel 11)
    - Port of New York Authority
      - Celler Hearings, 1960 November 28 (Reel 11)
      - Richard Kane (Reel 11)
      - Authority World Trade Center Hudson and Manhattan Railroad (Reel 11)
      - General (Reel 11)
      - General (Reel 12)
    - Port of Oswego Authority (Reel 12)
    - Power Authority Power Contracts (Reel 12)
    - Power Authority (Reel 12)
    - Rochester Monroe County Port Authority (Reel 12)
    - Saratoga Springs Authority (Reel 12)
    - Thruway Authority (Reel 12)
    - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Authority (Reel 12)
    - Water Resources Planning Commission (Reel 12)
    - Waterfront Commission on New York Harbor
      - 1961-1962 (Reel 12)
      - 1959-1960 (Reel 13)
    - White Plains Parkway Authority (Reel 13)
    - World's Fair Commission (Reel 13)
    - World War Memorial Authority (Reel 13)
    - Others (Reel 13)
    - General (Reel 13)
  - Banking (Reel 13)
    - Department of (Reel 13)
    - General (Reel 13)
      - Banks (Reel 13)
      - K. Blanche Brady (Reel 13)
      - Mergers (Reel 13)
      - Mortgages (Reel 13)
      - New York Clearing House Banks Luncheon, 1961 May 25 (Reel 13)
      - General (Reel 13)
  - Civil Defense (Reel 13, Reel 14, Reel 15, Reel 16)
    - Federal (Reel 13)
      - National Plan (Reel 13)
      - Operations Alert (Reel 13)
      - White House Conference (Reel 13)
      - General (Reel 13)
    - Certificates (Reel 13)
    - State (Reel 13, Reel 14, Reel 15, Reel 16)
      - Citizen's Survival Program (Reel 13)
      - Defense Council (Reel 13)
      - Committee, 1959 (Reel 14)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on Fallout Protection (Reel 14)
      - McHugh Reports (Reel 14)
      - Radioactive Fallout (Reel 14)
        - Task Force Report (Reel 14)
        - General (Reel 14)
      - Special State Committee on Recovery from Nuclear Attack (Reel 14)
      - Recovery Shelters
        - Con
          - 1962 (Reel 14)
          - 1960-1961 (Reel 15)
        - Pro (Reel 15)
        - School Programs (Reel 15)
        - General (Reel 15)
      - General (Reel 16)
  - Commerce (Reel 16, Reel 17, Reel 18, Reel 19)
    - Department of
      - Aviation (Reel 16)
        - Airports (Reel 16)
          - idlewild (Reel 16)
          - Pine Islands (Reel 16)
          - Others (Reel 16)
          - General (Reel 16)
      - Business Promotion (Reel 16)
        - Chicago Office (Reel 16)
        - Conventions (Reel 16)
        - International Bobsled Championship (Reel 16)
        - Los Angeles Office (Reel 16)
        - Montreal Office (Reel 16)
        - Operation Sail (Reel 16)
        - State Science & Technology Foundation (Reel 16)
        - General (Reel 16)
      - Business Publicity (Reel 16)
      - Business Research (Reel 16)
        - Advisory Council (Reel 16)
        - General (Reel 16)
      - Business Service
        - Hudson River Brick Industry (Reel 16)
        - Remington Rand Plant at Cobleskill (Reel 16)
        - Republic Aviation Corporation (Reel 17)
      - Radio, TV & Motion Pictures
        - "At the Source" (Reel 17)
        - "Continental Class Room" (Reel 17)
        - Governor's Schedule and Transportation (Reel 17)
        - "The Great Challenge" (Reel 17)
        - "Meet the Press" (Reel 17)
        - "Open end" (Reel 17)
        - "Opinion" (Reel 17)
        - "Your future in New York" (Reel 17)
        - General
          - 1961 July-1962 (Reel 17)
          - 1959-1961 June (Reel 18)
    - Travel (Reel 18)
    - 1962 U.S. World Trade (Reel 18)
    - Fair Washington Offices (Reel 18)
    - Women's Council (Reel 18)
    - 1964 World's Fair
      - 1961-1962 (Reel 18)
      - 1959-1960 (Reel 19)
    - General (Reel 19)
    - General (Reel 19)
      - Office of Regional Development (Reel 19)
      - World's Fair Center (Reel 19)
      - General (Reel 19)
  - Conservation (Reel 19, Reel 20)
    - Department of (Reel 19, Reel 20)
      - Aircraft (Reel 19)
      - Atlantic States Marine Fisheries (Reel 19)
      - Fish & Game (Reel 19)
        - Doe Season (Reel 19)
        - General (Reel 19)
      - Interstate Oil Compact Commission (Reel 19)
      - Lands & Forests (Reel 19)
        - National Lead Company (Reel 19)
        - General (Reel 19)
      - Long Island State Park Commission (Reel 19)
      - Division of Motor Boats (Reel 19)
      - Northeast Forest Fire Protection Committee (Reel 19)
      - Interdepartmental Commission on Pesticides (Reel 19)
      - Water Resources
        - Commission on (Reel 19)
        - Canadaigua Lake (Reel 19)
        - Great Lakes Commission (Reel 19)
        - National Research Symposium (Reel 19)
        - Saline Water Conversion (Reel 20)
        - Susquehanna River Basin (Reel 20)
        - General (Reel 20)
        - General (Reel 20)
    - General (Reel 20)
      - Lake George Encroachments (Reel 20)
      - General (Reel 20)
  - Consumer (Reel 20)
    - Problems of (Reel 20)
  - Correction (Reel 20)
    - Department (Reel 20)
    - Institution (Reel 20)
      - Attica (Reel 20)
      - Clinton-Daquemora (Reel 20)
      - Green Haven (Reel 20)
      - Matteawan (Reel 20)
      - Pharsalia (Reel 20)
      - Sing Sing (Reel 20)
      - Others (Reel 20)
      - General (Reel 20)
    - Parole (Reel 20)
      - Division of (Reel 20)
      - Governor's Committee (Reel 20)
      - General (Reel 20)
        - Congress on Correction (Reel 20)
        - Study of Condemned Prisoner's Sanity (Reel 20)
        - General (Reel 21)
  - Disasters (Reel 21)
    - Floods (Reel 21)
      - Flood Control (Reel 21)
        - Keuka Lake (Reel 21)
        - Kinzua Dam (Reel 21)
        - Others (Reel 21)
        - General (Reel 21)
      - General (Reel 21)
    - Truck Accidents (Reel 21)
    - Others (Reel 21)
      - Drought (Reel 21)
      - Fire (Reel 21)
      - Hurricanes (Reel 21)
      - Storms (Reel 21)
      - Snow (Reel 21)
      - Others (Reel 21)
  - Discrimination (Reel 21, Reel 22)
    - Commission Against (Reel 21)
      - Printed Reports & Materials (Reel 21)
      - Rochester Office (Reel 21)
      - General (Reel 21)
    - Anti-Semitism (Reel 21)
      - Nazi Rally (Reel 21)
      - General (Reel 21)
    - General (Reel 22)
      - Civil Rights Governor's Conference (Reel 22)
      - Race Religion & Civil Rights (Reel 22)
        - Martin Luther King (Reel 22)
        - Dr. Piervon (Reel 22)
        - General (Reel 22)
      - Code of Unfair Practices (Reel 22)
      - Employment (Reel 22)
        - City College (Reel 22)
        - Public Schools (Reel 22)
        - General (Reel 22)
      - Freedom Riders (Reel 22)
      - Hospitals (Reel 22)
      - Housing (Reel 22)
        - United Nations Delegate (Reel 22)
        - General (Reel 22)
      - General (Reel 22)
  - Education (Reel 22, Reel 23, Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26, Reel 27, Reel 28, Reel 29, Reel 30)
    - Department of (Reel 22, Reel 23)
      - Child Development & Patient Education (Reel 22)
      - State Library (Reel 22)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation
        - 1960-1962 (Reel 22)
        - 1959 (Reel 23)
        - General (Reel 23)
    - Finances (Reel 23)
      - Federal Aid (Reel 23)
      - State Aid (Reel 23)
      - Marketing of School of School Bonds (Reel 23)
      - General
        - 1959 October-1962 (Reel 23)
        - 1962 January-September (Reel 24)
    - Museums & Historical Sites (Reel 24)
      - Albany Institute of History & Art (Reel 24)
      - Albright Art Gallery (Reel 24)
      - American Museum of Natural History (Reel 24)
      - Boscobel Mansion (Reel 24)
      - Carnegie Hall (Reel 24)
      - Clinton House (Reel 24)
      - Thomas Cole House (Reel 24)
      - Colonial Williamsburg (Reel 24)
      - Emancipation Proclamation (Reel 24)
      - Guy Park Mansion (Reel 24)
      - Alexander Hamilton Home (Reel 24)
      - Hudson Champlain Celebration (Reel 24)
      - Lincoln Center (Reel 24)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art (Reel 24)
      - Military Museum State Capital (Reel 24)
      - Museum of Modern Art (Reel 24)
      - Pennsylvania Station (Reel 24)
      - Whitney Museum (Reel 24)
      - Year of History (Reel 24)
      - Other Historical Sites (Reel 24)
      - General (Reel 24)
    - Schools (Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26)
      - High & Elementary (Reel 24)
        - Caroline G. Atkinson Elementary School (Reel 24)
        - Aviation High School (Reel 24)
        - Charlton School (Reel 24)
        - Emma Willard School (Reel 24)
        - St. Agnes School (Reel 24)
        - Others (Reel 24)
      - Colleges & Universities (Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26)
        - Agriculture & Technical Institutes (Reel 24)
        - Albany Graduate Program in Public Administration (Reel 24)
        - Albany Medical School (Reel 24)
        - Albany State Teachers College (Reel 24)
        - Brandeis University (Reel 24)
        - Brooklyn College (Reel 24)
        - Brown University (Reel 24)
        - University of Buffalo (Reel 24)
        - College of Education at Buffalo (Reel 24)
        - University of California (Berkeley and Los Angeles) (Reel 24)
        - Chautauqua Institute (Reel 24)
        - University of Chicago (Reel 25)
        - City College (Reel 25)
        - Colgate University (Reel 25)
        - University of Colorado (Reel 25)
        - Columbia University (Reel 25)
        - Concordia College (Reel 25)
        - Cornell University (Reel 25)
          - N.Y State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (Reel 25)
          - Others (Reel 25)
        - College of Education at Cortland (Reel 25)
        - Dartmouth College (Reel 25)
        - Down State Medical School (Reel 25)
        - Drew University (Reel 25)
        - Albert Einstein College of Medicine (Reel 25)
        - Fordham University (Reel 25)
        - Harper College (Reel 25)
        - Hobart and William Smith (Reel 25)
        - Hofstra College (Reel 25)
        - Hunter College (Reel 25)
        - Illinois University (Reel 25)
        - Indiana University (Reel 25)
        - Iowa State University (Reel 25)
        - Kansas State University (Reel 25)
        - State University Colleges on Long Island (Reel 25)
        - Martime College, Fort Schuyler (Reel 25)
        - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Reel 25)
        - Meharry Medical College (Reel 25)
        - Mexico City College (Reel 25)
        - Miami University (Reel 25)
        - Michigan State University (Reel 25)
        - Michigan University (Reel 25)
        - Mills College of Education (Reel 25)
        - Moravian College (Reel 25)
        - Nassau Community College (Reel 25)
        - College of Education at New Paltz (Reel 25)
        - New York University (Reel 25)
        - Northwestern University (Reel 25)
        - Notre Dame (Reel 25)
        - Ohio State University (Reel 25)
        - Orange County Community College (Reel 25)
        - College of Education at Oswego (Reel 25)
        - Pace College (Reel 25)
        - Pennsylvania College (Reel 25)
        - University of Pittsburgh (Reel 25)
        - Plattsburgh Teachers College (Reel 25)
        - Princeton University (Reel 25)
        - Queens College (Reel 25)
        - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (Reel 25)
        - University of Rochester (Reel 25)
        - Rutgers University (Reel 25)
        - Saint John University (Reel 25)
        - Saint Lawrence University (Reel 25)
        - Siena College (Reel 25)
        - Skidmore College (Reel 25)
        - Springfield College (Reel 25)
        - Stanford University (Reel 25)
        - Stephens College (Reel 25)
        - Syracuse University (Reel 25)
        - University of Toledo (Reel 25)
        - Union College (Reel 25)
        - Union Technological Seminary (Reel 25)
        - United States Military Academy (Reel 25)
        - Utah State University (Reel 25)
        - Vassar College (Reel 25)
        - Virginia University (Reel 25)
        - Wagener College (Reel 25)
        - Wayne State (Reel 25)
        - Wellesley College (Reel 25)
        - Westchester Community College (Reel 25)
        - Willamette University (Reel 25)
        - Wilmington College (Reel 25)
        - University of Wisconsin (Reel 25)
        - Yale University (Reel 25)
        - Yeshiva University (Reel 25)
        - Others (Reel 25)
          - A-D (Reel 25)
        - General (Reel 26)
          - E-V (Reel 26)
      - Others (Reel 26)
        - New York Institute for Education of the Blind (Reel 26)
      - State University (Reel 26)
        - Board of Trustees (Reel 26)
        - Proposed Community Colleges (Reel 26)
        - Scholarships (Reel 26)
          - Congratulations (Reel 26)
          - Thank You's (Reel 26)
          - General (Reel 26)
        - Construction Fund (Reel 26)
        - General (Reel 26)
    - General (Reel 26, Reel 27, Reel 28, Reel 29, Reel 30)
      - Adult Education (Reel 26)
      - Advisory Council for Advancement of Scientific Research (Reel 26)
      - Arts Council (Reel 27)
      - Class Size (Reel 27)
      - Driver Education (Reel 27)
      - Educational Television (Reel 27)
      - Higher Education
        - Higher Education Assistance Corp (Reel 27)
        - Heald Report (Reel 27)
        - Medical Education (Reel 27)
        - People to People (Reel 27)
          - Acknowledgements (Reel 27)
          - Background (Reel 27)
        - Incentive Program
          - 1961 February 24-1962 (Reel 27)
          - 1959-1961 February 23 (Reel 28)
        - New York University Doctorate Report (Reel 28)
        - Tuition (Reel 28)
        - General (Reel 28)
      - Libraries (Reel 28)
      - Local Problems (Reel 28)
        - General (Reel 28)
        - Elwood School District (Reel 28)
        - Levittown (Reel 28)
        - New York City (Reel 28)
        - Westhill (Reel 28)
        - General (Reel 28)
      - Loyalty Oath (Reel 29)
      - Retarded & Handicapped Children (Reel 29)
      - School Buses (Reel 29)
      - Students in Politics (Reel 29)
        - Letters to Editors (Reel 29)
        - Letters to Presidents (Reel 29)
        - Others (Reel 29)
      - White House Conference on Education (Reel 29)
      - General
        - 1960-1962 (Reel 29)
        - 1959 (Reel 30)
  - Executive Clemency (Reel 30)
    - Morgan D. Ryan (Reel 30)
    - General (Reel 30)
  - Extradition (Reel 30)
    - Willie Reid (Reel 30)
    - General (Reel 30)
  - Fiscal (Reel 30, Reel 31, Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36)
    - Accounting (Reel 30)
      - Department of Audit & Control (Reel 30)
      - Accounting Improvement Papers (Reel 30)
      - General (Reel 30)
    - Budget (Reel 30, Reel 31)
      - Division of
        - 1962 (Reel 30)
        - 1959-1961 (Reel 31)
      - Summary (Reel 31)
      - Memo (Reel 31)
      - General (Reel 31)
      - Annual Budgets (Reel 31)
    - Expenditures (Reel 31, Reel 32)
      - Office of General Services (Reel 31)
        - Standards & Purchases (Reel 31)
          - Activity Reports (Reel 31)
          - Herald Square Press (Reel 31)
          - Manhattan Lighting and Equipment Company (Reel 31)
          - Simmons Machine Tool Company (Reel 31)
          - William Speers (Reel 31)
          - General (Reel 31)
          - Division of (Reel 31)
        - Central Operations (Reel 31)
          - State Cars for Legislators (Reel 31)
          - Roosevelt Packard (Reel 31)
          - State Cars General (Reel 31)
        - General (Reel 31)
      - General (Reel 32)